Wh-What is all this?
Poke, poke.
Oh, no! It's a trap!
Wait, what is?!
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
Day 9: The Arrival of Winter
One month after the harvest
season of autumn...
The seasons changed in the blink of an eye,
and Tempest was preparing
to greet the winter.
The wind really turned cold
fast in these past few days.
Yes, it is winter now.
Everyone, make sure you dress warm.
Even with resistances,
you don't want to get careless.
By the way, I had this made!
A padded kimono? It looks nice and warm.
I can't let everyone see me
looking like I'm about to freeze.
But aren't you naked when
you're in your slime form?
Huh?
Oh...
...dear.
Oh, Great Rimuru!
Naked...
You know, she's right!
I'm buck naked right now!
I'm just strutting around
in my birthday suit!
Great Rimuru!
Greetings, Great Rimuru.
Hello, Great Rimuru!
Hi!
Oh, no! What is this feeling?
It's Great Rimuru!
Hello!
My cheeks feel warm...
Hiya...
Wait! This isn't the time to be shy!
I was assembling everyone
at the guard station!
Guard
So, as you all know,
most of this town is made of wood.
Fire Awareness
And it'll soon be getting colder and colder.
People will be making fires for warmth,
which increases the risk of house fires.
So you'll need to both patrol
and talk to people more every day.
We'll call it the Fire Awareness Campaign.
For
Great
Rimuru
Only
The campaign mascot, who specializes
in the subject, is this guy!
Winter Fire Awareness
Fire Awareness
Let's Burn
Protect the Town by Being Prepared
Tempest Fire Prevention Campaign Mascot
Benimaru
Be careful of fire!
Um... I don't... think I like this.
Huh? Why?
Let's Burn
I look like an arsonist.
Be careful of fire!
Healing Potion Research Lab
Heya!
Ah, it's you, Great Rimuru.
It's not as bad as outside,
but it's pretty cold in here, too.
Yes. I'm studying its effects
on the growth of hipokute herbs.
How's it going for you, Gabiru?
Yes... Vesta.
It's growing just fine.
Good, good.
Wait, when it's winter, do you Dragonewts...
What are you saying?!
No matter what the season is, I am fully
alert and aware when carrying... out...
my duties...
at... all... times...
Well, the peace and quiet
do make it easier to work.
Uh... your face looks creepy.
Oh, Great Rimuru!
*Dragonewt hibernation habits vary among individuals.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
You're asleep, aren't you?
Slime! ... Diaries...
Treant Forest
I'm Apito.
I'm Zegion.
Today is another day of gathering nectar.
Indeed.
There aren't many flowers in winter.
We need to work hard.
We got a lot, huh?
Indeed.
For Delivery
That'll do it.
Now, we must deliver it to Great Rimuru.
Tempest, the paradise for monsters...
Indeed.
Manual labor is a great thing.
Peace is a great thing.
Bug! Bug!
There's one!
Hey, that honey...
I just want a little taste of that honey.
Honey...
Just a little lick... One little lick...
Lady Milim!
Please stop bullying the weak.
Come, now. You'll make Great Rimuru
sad if only you get to taste it.
Aw...
Very well.
That was scary...
Indeed...
We must get stronger.
Shuna, I'm going out to train.
Wow, it feels so soft.
I can have this?
Of course.
I'm so happy you like it.
For Brother
You're supposed to wear
those when you sleep.
What does it matter? They're warm.
Your horns are warm?
My horns are also warm.
I will be brief.
We are currently roaming the Forest of Jura.
Our goal is the city of monsters.
Yes...
The town...
...where Shizu died.
You can't be sad forever, okay?
And also the town that had
the delicious grilled meat!
Huh?
Oh, I remember that meat!
It was so nice.
I hope we get there soon.
I'm so hungry...
What?!
Stop dawdling, you three!
Right...
Remember me sometimes, okay?
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
Slime Diaries.
It's not fair that One Horn
gets Rimuru all the time!
It's Shion.
Yeah, that!
Me, too! Me, too! Let me hold him, too!
To carry Great Rimuru means
to take up his noble ideals, as well
as the destiny of this entire nation.
It does?
Those feelings and their gravity
are so great that even Princess Shuna
cannot be entrusted with them.
Just give him to me already!
That's wrong! Hold Great Rimuru up higher!
Walk at a relaxed pace,
and keep your strides even!
Your back is bent!
What's the matter, Demon Lord?
You'll never be a great secretary that way!
Shion, why only at times like these?
It's hard to walk like this!
Revived!
Revived
Hey, uh, is there less of me?
You're imagining it!
Slime Diaries: to be continued!
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Slime Diaries
Guildmaster, I'm so hungry!
What's that?!
I-It's a Knight Spider!
Run!
You poked at its nest again, didn't you?!
Kaval, you idiot! Dorkaval!
Don't call me Dorkaval!
I'm Youm. Who are you people?
Huh?
Uh... I'm Fuze. Are you...
Kaval! I like grilled meat!
I'm Rommel. I have a weak stomach,
so I can't eat grilled meat.
I'm Eren! I want something warm
to eat! It's cold out!
Hey! That's not what
we should be talking—
I'm Gido! I like hotpot
and that kind of thing!
Hey!
Then we'll have hotpot for dinner!
Yay!
Who is that?!
Hey! Listen to me, people!
We arrived in Tempest without incident.
Ah, there you are! Kurobe, Kurobe!
Lady Milim! You came by to watch again?
Also, my name's Kurobei.
Yeah, that!
They get along so well.
What are you making today?
Today, I'm making a sword for Gobta.
When forging magisteel, you can't
let your guard down for a second!
Just... the slightest...
change in... your strike...
can produce either... a great sword...
or scrap metal!
It sure can!
Eh?!
Incredible!
A short sword that can
take down a Knight Spider!
Hmm... I guess all's well that ends well.
Got a cold?
So anyway, we have a visitor!
The humans have finally endeavored
to make contact with Great Rimuru.
As a caretaker of the forest,
I must carefully discern
what it is they truly want.
It has a kick to it. I like it.
And they have such an invigorating aroma.
I can't stop eating them.
Hey! You guys are taking too much!
Wh-What?
My new winter potato chip
flavor is that popular?!
New Winter Flavor
-Yuzu and Pepper Flavor-
Clearly, those three are very good people.
There can be no one bad among
those who love nature's blessings!
Then I shall have one, as well.
I'm sorry, but they said
they'd like seconds.
I'll fry up more.
Great Rimuru.
Regarding your cooperation
with the humans...
Please think it over very carefully.
O-Okay...
She never sounds that serious.
Does this issue really run that deep?
Our addictive new item has
a refreshing aroma and a touch of heat.
No one beats Snack Bar
Jura for potato chips!
A wonderful place where you can laugh without a care
Snack Bar
Jura
How would you like to be a champion?
What?
I want everyone to think you and your
buddies defeated the Orc Lord.
Huh?
And we'll spread rumors that the nation
of monsters will work together
with you brave youths
and give you our backing.
Then you'll go from being
wanted men to being champions,
and we'll get everyone to believe
we're friendly toward humans.
Hmm...
I get it!
Well, just think about it, okay?
I thought he was just a joker, but...
We cannot allow a guest to go hungry.
As if the boss wasn't weird enough,
so are his subordinates.
They're all constantly going on about
"Great Rimuru, Great Rimuru"...
Piping Hot
Great Rimuru Buns
Welcome!
They're piping hot!
You're Great Rimuru's guest, right? Here!
Huh?
Uh, sure...
Take this Great Rimuru mask!
O-Okay, uh... thanks...
Have some savory Great Rimuru crackers!
You must try our Great Rimuru soup!
Er, sorry...
Hey, you're not forgetting our
tri-colored Great Rimurus, are you?
Have some grilled Great Rimuru!
Great
Rimuru
Crackers
Tri-colored
Great
Rimurus
Rimuru
Dumplings
Revolving
Great
Rimuru
Buns
Hey! You've gotta check out
our revolving Great Rimuru, too!
They really love you, don't they?
It bugs me that they're all foods
that look like me, though.
So on that note...
This is Youm-kun and his buddies.
They'll be living with us as of today.
Treat them well!
Yeah, so... Hi.
The welcome feast is nearly ready.
Ooh! That's my Shuna!
I'll just go and check on it.
All right!
It's a banquet!
The food here is really good.
Banquet! Banquet! Banquet!
They're such good-natured people.
What the hell? So monsters
are no different from humans at all.
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
Yum! It's so good!
Tasty!
It's the one from earlier today...
It'll warm you right up.
They're monsters, all right.
Sorry. You get used to it.
A slime body doesn't need to breathe.
Okay... Great Sage!
Complete.
Complete
By controlling heat within the body,
Control heat
within body
Steam created
successfully
steam has been created successfully.
Adjust pressure
Adjusting the pressure will cause it
to release from the mouth.
Release
from mouth
Preparations complete.
Look! I made my breath white!
Huh? What are you talking
about, Great Rimuru?
Are you all right?
Maximum output.
Maximum output
What kind of technique is that?!
Stop playing around and start cleaning!
Preview
This is actually pretty good!
You're a real heavyweight, you know that?
Next time, "Snow Blankets
the City of Monsters."